Guide to the John L. Margrave academic papers, 1952-1995 MS 505
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VII: Meetings, 1970-1988, 220856
  - Spectroscopy of Matrix Isolated Species, 220931 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - SREB, Faculty Exchange Program, 220930 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - STTF, Proposal Review, June 26-27, 1979, 220929 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Sylvania Award Dinner, 220928 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Symposium on Thermonuclear Properties, 220927 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Synthetic Approach to Organometallic Chemistry, 220926 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - TAS, March 15-17, 1973, 220925 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - TAS, March 6-8, 1980, 220924 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Tech Exchange, 220923 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Technology Venturing, 220922 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Texas Academy of Science, March 10-12, 1977, 220921 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Texas Computer Industry Council, 220920 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Texas Independent College Fund, 220919 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Texas Institute of Chemists, September 26, 1978, 220918 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Texas Institute of Chemists, April 12, 1986, 220917 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Texas Lyceum, 220916 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Texas Philosophical Society, December 3-4, 1972, 220915 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Texas Philosophical Society, 1975, 220914 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Texas Philosophical Society, December 9-10, 1977, 220913 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Texas Philosophical Society, December 7-8, 1984, 220912 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Texas Philosophical Society, December 6-7, 1985, 220911 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Texas Southern University, Graduate School Day, November 20, 1975, 220910 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Texas Southern University, Presidential Search Committee, Correspondence, 1980, 220909 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Texas Southern University, Presidential Search Committee, Miscellaneous, 1980, 220908 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - U/ITT, January 15-17, 1985, 220907 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - U/ITT, Conference Summary, December 8-9, 1981, 220906 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - U/ITT, Correspondence, December 8-9, 1981, 220905 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - U/ITT, Finances, December 8-9, 1981, 220904 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - U/ITT, Participants, December 8-9, 1981, 220903 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - U/ITT, Sample Letters, December 8-9, 1981, 220902 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Union Carbide, 220901 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - University of Kansas Alumni Association, 220900 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - University of Tennessee, Chemistry Review, February 2-3, 1981, 220899 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - University of Texas at Austin, Centennial Convocation, 220898 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - University of Texas at San Antonio, Minority Center, 220897 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - URA, February 4, 1977, 220896 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - URA, February 2, 1978, 220895 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - URA, January 26, 1979, 220894 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - URA, February 8, 1980, 220893 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - URA, February 5, 1982, 220892 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Air Force, High Temperature Composites Initiative, October 22-23, 1985, 220891 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Air Force, Laser Hardened Materials Program Review, September 30-October 3, 1985, 220890 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - USARO, Molecular Spectroscopy, June 13-17, 1983, 220889 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - U.S. Army, Ballistic Missile Defense, June 1-2, 1977, 220888 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - U.S. Army, Chemical Stockpile, June 14, 1984, 220887 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Army, Chemical Stockpile, Suplecam Cycle II, Agent GC Curves for HD & HT AT ANAD, 220886 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - U.S. Army, Chemical Stockpile, Suplecame Cycle II, Test Results, 220885 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - U.S. Army, Chemical Stockpile, Suplecam Improvements, Milestone Charts, 220884 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - U.S. Army, Defense Against Chemical Agents, November 13-15, 1980, 220883 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - U.S. Army, High Pressure Phenomena, June 2-4, 1976, 220882 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - U.S. Army, High Temperature Synthesis, October 21-23, 1985, 220881 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - U.S. Army, Semi-Annual Review DARPA Advanced Materials Program, February 5-6, 1985, 220880 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - USRA, March 25, 1982, 220879 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Vought, October 30, 1980, 220878 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Vought, August 16, 1983, 220877 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Vought, August 29, 1983, 220876 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Welch Foundation, November 5-7, 1973, 220875 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Welch Foundation, November 11-13, 1974, 220874 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Welch Foundation, October 29-31, 1975, 220873 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Welch Foundation, November 8-10, 1976, 220872 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Welch Foundation, November 7-9, 1977, 220871 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Welch Foundation, November 6-8, 1978, 220870 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Welch Foundation, November 12-14, 1979, 220869 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Welch Foundation, November 10-12, 1980, 220868 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Welch Foundation, November 9-11, 1981, 220867 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Welch Foundation, November 15-17, 1982, 220866 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Welch Foundation, November 7-9, 1983, 220865 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Welch Foundation, November 5-7, 1984, 220864 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Welch Foundation, November 4, 1985, 220863 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Welch Foundation, November 3-5, 1986, 220862 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Welch Foundation, October 31-November 2, 1988, 220861 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Welch Foundation, Board Meeting, March 6, 1985, 220860 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Welch Foundation, Lectures, November 11-15, 1985, 220859 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Western Name Exchange, 220858 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - W. O. Milligan Symposium, 220857 (Box 27, Folder 45)
- Series VIII: National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), 1971-1982, 220829
  Within the National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) series is information related to a materials research grant Margrave had from 1971 through 1978, as well as information connected with the Space Shuttle and space science.
  - Correspondence, 220855 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Materials Research Grant, 1971, 220854 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Materials Research Grant, 1972, 220853 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Materials Research Grant, 1973, 220852 (Box 28, Folder 4-5)
  - Materials Research Grant, 1974, 220851 (Box 28, Folder 6-7)
  - Materials Research Grant, 1975, 220850 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Materials Research Grant, 1976, 220849 (Box 28, Folder 9-10)
  - Materials Research Grant, 1977, 220848 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Materials Research Grant, 1978, 220847 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Meetings, 1972, 220846 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Meetings, 1976, 220845 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Meetings, Material Processing (Space Shuttle), 1982, 220844 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Meetings, Material Research Society, 1981, 220843 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Meetings, Microgravitivity Workshop, 1978, 220842 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Meetings, Space Processing Payload Advisory Subcommittee, 1976, 220841 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Meetings, Space Shuttle Experiments, 1976, 220840 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Microgravity Materials Science Conference Publication, October 1996, 220839 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous, 220838 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Publications, 220837 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Reports, 220836 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Space Commercialization, 220835 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Space Processing Payload Advisory Subcommittee, Briefing Material, February 18-19, 1976, 220834 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Space Processing Payload Advisory Subcommittee, Correspondence, 220833 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Space Processing Payload Advisory Subcommittee, Margrave Educational Data Survey, 220832 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Space Processing Payload Advisory Subcommittee, Miscellaneous, 220831 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Space Science Working Group, 220830 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- Series IX: Research Group, 1964-1979, 220754
  The Research Group series includes files associated with the individuals involved in research with Margrave. They include not only members of the Rice Chemistry Department, but also those individuals outside of the university with whom Margrave was involved.
  Researchers are also encouraged to look in Series II: Correspondence (Boxes 2 and 3) and Series XI: Rice, General Correspondence (Boxes 36 and 37) for other letters of recommendation.
  - Albritton, Lee, 220828 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Alper, Allen, 220827 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Ames, Lynford, 220826 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Badachhape, R. B., 220825 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Billups, Ed, 220824 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Binenboym. J., 220823 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Blue, Gary, 220822 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Bonnell, David, 220821 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Bunch, David, 220820 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Burfitt, Carol, 220819 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 220818 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Curl, Robert, 220817 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Dadape, V. V., 220816 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - DeKock, Carroll, 220815 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Demorest, Keith, 220814 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Engel, Paul, 220813 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Ettlinger, Martin, 220812 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Franklin, Joe, 220811 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Gansow, Otto, 220810 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Garrett, Mark, 220809 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Glass, G., 220808 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Gole, James, 220807 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Gore, Ronald, 220806 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Gurvich, L., 220805 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Hadley, Fred, 220804 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Hamill, Delphia, 220803 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Hastie, John, 220802 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Haug, Pat, 220801 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Hauge, Robert, 220800 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Hayes, Richard, 220799 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Hendricks, James, 220798 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Hepler, Loren, 220797 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Hudson, James, 220796 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Ismail, Zizi, 220795 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Kamarchik, Peter, Correspondence, 220794 (Box 29, Folder 35-36)
  - Kamarchik, Peter, Miscellaneous, 220793 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Kamarchik, Peter, Papers, 220792 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Kana'an, Adli, 220791 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Kowanko, Nicholas, 220790 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Krishnan, Coimbatore, 220789 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Kunze, Ken, 220788 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Kurth, Matthias, 220787 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Lagow, R. J., 220786 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Lists, 220785 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Mahajan, Vijay, 220784 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Matsumoto, Osamu, 220783 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Melaugh, Robert, 220782 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, 220781 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Moore, Timothy, 220780 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Moravan, Kou-Ying, 220779 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Mosier, Benjamin, 220778 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Muenow, David, 220777 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Papantoni-Kazakos, Tharakos, 220776 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Peacock, R. D., 220775 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Pederson, John, 220774 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Perry, Dale, 220773 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Phillips, William, 220772 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Pichat, Philippe, 220771 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Sharp, Kenneth, 220770 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Skell, Philip, 220769 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Spielvogel, Bernard, 220768 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Srivastava, Rameshwar, 220767 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Stafford, Fred, 220766 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Stevens, Robert, 220765 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Subach, Daniel, 220764 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Timms, Peter, 220763 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Thomas, J. M., 220762 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Varma, Ravi, 220761 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Wagner, Lawrence, 220760 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Wall, F. T., 220759 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Wenkert, Ernest, 220758 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Wilhelm, Mark, 220757 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Williams, Dennis, 220756 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Wilson, Paul, 220755 (Box 30, Folder 37)
- Series X: Reviews/Proposals, 1969-1985, 220685
  The series Reviews/Proposals contains records related to reviews Margrave wrote and proposals Margrave conducted. This includes manuscript reviews Margrave did for journals other than High Temperature Science, and research proposals he submitted to entities such as the Department of Energy, the National Science Foundation, and the Welch Foundation.
  - Subseries A: Reviews, 220736
    - CRSSR, Correspondence, 220753 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - CRSSR, List of Panelists, 220752 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - CRSSR, Miscellaneous, 220751 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - CRSSR, Notes, 220750 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - CRSSR, Other Reports, 220749 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - CRSSR, Reimbursement, 220748 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - CRSSR, Report, 220747 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Manuscripts Reviewed, Journal of the American Chemical Society, 1969-1975, 220746 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Manuscripts Reviewed, Journal of the American Chemical Society1976-1981, 220745 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Manuscripts, Reviewed, Miscellaneous, 1970, 220744 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Manuscripts Reviews, Miscellaneous, 1971, 220743 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Manuscripts Reviewed, Miscellaneous, 1972, 220742 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Manuscripts Reviewed, Miscellaneous, 1973, 220741 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Manuscripts Reviewed, Miscellaneous, 1974, 220740 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Manuscripts Reviewed, Miscellaneous, 1975-, 220739 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Manuscripts Reviewed, NRC, 1973-1976, 220738 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Manuscripts Reviewed, NSF, 1969-1981, 220737 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Subseries B: Proposals, 220686
    - A Quantum Electronics Institute, 220735 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Advanced Technology Program; Production of Large CVD Thin Wall Diamond Shapes, 220734 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Air Force Flight Test Center; The Formation, Isolation, and Characterization of the Neutral Ammonium Species, 220733 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - ACS; Preparation, Structure and Reactions of the Alkali Metal Carbonyls, 220732 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute; Emissivities, Reflectivities, Viscosities and Surface Tensions of Pure Liquid Iron and of Selected Iron Alloys, 220731 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - AROD; various, 220730 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - ARPA; Fluorochemical Substitutes for Blood, 220729 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Battelle; Study to Determine the Corrosion Fatigue Behavior of Aluminum Tubes, 220728 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - BDM; Laser Pyrolysis Studies, 220727 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Cameron Iron Works; Development of Fluorinated Rubber for Use in Oil Fields, 220726 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Containerless Evaporation of Superheated Silicon, 220725 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - DOE; various, 220724 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - DOE; Coal, Contractor's Meetings, 220723 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - DOE; Coal, Correspondence, 220722 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - DOE; Coal, Papers, 220721 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - DOE; Coal, Papers, 220720 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - DOE; Coal, Notes, 220719 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - DOE; Coal, Proposals, 220718 (Box 32, Folder 1-3)
    - DOE; Coal, Technical Reports, 220717 (Box 32, Folder 4-6)
    - Dow Chemical, 220716 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Energy Resource Packet for High School Teachers, 220715 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - ERDA, 220714 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Fluoro Products, Inc. (CFX and FluoroKote), 220713 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - HEW, 220712 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - High Temperature Composites, 220711 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Materials Science Research Center; The High-Temperature Research Laboratory, 220710 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 220709 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous correespondence, 220708 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - NASA; Centers for the Commercial Development of Space, 220707 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Non-Contact Thermal, Physical Property Measurements of Multicomponent-Multiphase Systems, 220706 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - NSERC (SERI), 220705 (Box 32, Folder 18-19)
    - NSF, 220704 (Box 32, Folder 20-24)
    - NSF, By Others, 220703 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - NSF, Correspondence, 220702 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Petroleum Research Fund; Reactions of Carbon Atoms and Silicon Atoms with Water, 220701 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Reviewed by Margrave, 220700 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Sea Grant College Program, 220699 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - STTF; A New Solar Energy Design, 220698 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Submitted by Advanced Studies and Research, General File, 220697 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Temperature Measurement; Design, Construction and Testing of Divison of Amplitude Polarimetric Pyrometer, 220696 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Thermodynamic and Kinetic Studies of Materials at High Temperatures and/or High Pressures, 220695 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Training Program for Rice Personnel in Clerical, Secretarial, and Intermediate Level Employment, 220694 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Ultech/Perkin Elmer; Studies of Reactive Species in Plasma, 220693 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - U.S. Army, 220692 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - U.S. Bureau of Mines; Fluorine and Its Importance, 220691 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - U.S. Energy Research Administration; New Synthesis of Organic Chemicals Based on Carbon Monoxide as a Starting Material, 220690 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Welch Foundation, 220689 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Welch Foundation; Chemistry Under Extreme Conditions, 220688 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Welch Foundation; Partial Endowment of Rice Chemistry, 220687 (Box 32, Folder 41)
- Series XI: Rice University, 1970-1989, 220479
  Researchers are also encouraged to look in Series II: Correspondence (Boxes 2 and 3) and Series IX: Research Group (Boxes 29 and 30) for other letters of recommendation.
  - AAU Site Visit, February 17, 1984, 220684 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - AAUP, 220683 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Academic Calendars, 220682 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Academic Deans' Meetings, Agendas, 220681 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Academic Deans' Meetins, Correspondence, 220680 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Academic Deans' Meetings, Miscellaneous, 220679 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Academic Deans' Meetings, Reports, 220678 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Advanced Studies and Research Office, 220677 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Advanced Studies and Research, Grants, 220676 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Affirmative Action Recruiting Procedures, 220675 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Leaders' Workshop, 220674 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Architecture Department, 220673 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Art and Art History Department, 220672 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Baker College Honor Course in Research, 220671 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Bicentennial Lecture -- "Can We Preserve the Wild Blue Yonder?", 220670 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Biochemistry Department, 220669 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Biology Department, 220668 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Biomedical Engineering Department, 220667 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Biomedical Engineering Lab, 220666 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Board of Governors, 220665 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Bonner Nuclear Lab, 220664 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Brazil Briefing, 220663 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Brown School of Engineering, 220662 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Business Appreciation Day, 220661 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Business Office, 220660 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Building Inspections, 220659 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Department Meetings, Correspondence, 220658 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Department Meetings, Minutes, 1972, 220657 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Department Meetings, Minutes, 1973, 220656 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Department Meetings, Minutes, 1974, 220655 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Department Meetings, Minutes, 1975, 220654 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Department Meetings, Minutes, 1976, 220653 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Department Meetings, Minutes, 1977-78, 220652 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Department Meetings, Minutes, 1982-84, 220651 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Department Meetings, Miscellaneous, 220650 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Chemistry Lectures, Asano, Dr. Mitsuru, 220649 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Chemistry Lectures, Catalano, Dr. Edward, 220648 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Chemistry Lectures, Dye, Dr. James, 220647 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Chemistry Lectures, Glaunsinger, Dr. W. S., 220646 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Chemistry Lectures, Komarek, Kurt, 220645 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Chemistry Lectures, Leribaux, Dr. Henri, 220644 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Chemistry Lectures, Parry, Dr. Robert, 220643 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Chemistry Lectures, Poliakoff, Martyn, 220642 (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Chemistry Lectures, Roesky, Dr. Herbert, 220641 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Chemistry Lectures, Woodward, Dr. Robert, 220640 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Commencement, 1974, 220639 (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Commencement, 1975, 220638 (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Commencement, 1976, 220637 (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - Commencement, 1977, 220636 (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - Commencement, 1978, 220635 (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - Commencement, 1979, 220634 (Box 33, Folder 51)
  - Commencement, 1980, 220633 (Box 33, Folder 52)
  - Commencement, 1981, 220632 (Box 33, Folder 53)
  - Commencement, 1982, 220631 (Box 33, Folder 54)
  - Commencement, 1983, 220630 (Box 33, Folder 55)
  - Commencement, 1985, 220629 (Box 33, Folder 56)
  - Committees, Academic Affairs, 220628 (Box 33, Folder 57)
  - Committees, Academic Affairs, SACS, 1975, 220627 (Box 33, Folder 58-59)
  - Committees, Academic Planning Subcommittee on Organization and Financing of Research, 220626 (Box 33, Folder 60)
  - Committees, Ad Hoc MD/PHD Program, 220625 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Committees, Affirmative Action, 220624 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Committees, Architectural Dean Search, 220623 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Committees, Engineering Advisory Council; Agendas, Assignments, and Rosters, 220622 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Committees, Engineering Advisory Council, Correspondence, 220621 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Committees, Engineering Advisory Council, Minutes, 220620 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Committees, Engineering Advisory Council, Miscellaneous, 220619 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Committees, Engineering Advisory Council, Notes, 220618 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Committees, Health Sciences, 220617 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Committees, Honors, 220616 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Committees, Space Assignment, 220615 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Committees, Undergraduate Teaching, 220614 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Committees, University Coordinating, 220613 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Comptroller, 220612 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Convocations, Hackerman, Dr. Norman, 220611 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Convocations, Homecoming, 220610 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Dean of Undergraduate Affairs, 220609 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Department Chairs' Meetings, 220608 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Economics Department, 220607 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Engineering Department, 220606 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - English Department, 220605 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Environmental Science and Engineering Department, 220604 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - ESCA, Correspondence, 220603 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - ESCA, Miscellaneous, 220602 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - ESCA, Miscellaneous, 220601 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - ESCA, Questionnaires, 220600 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Exxon Joint Program, 220599 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Faculty Attitudes toward Research at Rice, 220598 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Faculty Council, Correspondence, 220597 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Faculty Council, Minutes, 220596 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Faculty Council, Miscellaneous, 220595 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Faculty Meetings, Correspondence, 220594 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Faculty Meetings, Minutes, 220593 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Faculty Reports to the President, 220592 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Financial Aid, 220591 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Fondren Library, 220590 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Foreign Languages Department, 220589 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Foreign Student Orientation, 220588 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Geology Department, 220587 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Graduate Council, Correspondence, 220586 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Graduate Council, Minutes, 220585 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Graduate Council, Miscellaneous, 220584 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - The Graduate House, 220583 (Box 34, Folder 43)